Can't Buy My Love is a romance, tv movie film directed by Farhad Mann.
Lilly, a hard working EMT, is only focused on her
job and getting into medical school.
So when wealthy slacker Jeff enters her life it throws her off course.
At first, Lilly wants nothing to do with Jeff or his
sense of entitlement and lack of direction.
As she spends more time with him, she starts to realize that
you can’t always judge a book by its cover.
Lilly, played by Adelaide Kane.
Jeff, played by Benjamin Hollingsworth.
Rex, played by James Remar.
Veronica, played by Jean Louisa Kelly.
Nick, played by Rodrigo Rojas.
Megan, played by Andrea Bordeaux.
"Can't Help Falling in Love" is a song written by Hugo Peretti, Luigi
Creatore, and George David Weiss and published by Gladys Music, Inc.
The melody is based on "Plaisir d'amour", a popular French love
song composed in 1784 by Jean-Paul-Égide Martini.
The song was initially written from the perspective of a woman as "Can't Help Falling in Love with Him",
which explains the first and third line ending on "in" rather than words rhyming with "you".
Recorded by singer and actor Elvis Presley, it was part of the album Blue
Hawaii (1961), the soundtrack to the movie Blue Hawaii.
The song was recorded subsequently in the 1960s by Perry Como, the Lennon Sisters,
Doris Day, Patti Page, Andy Williams, Al Martino and Keely Smith.
In the 1970s, the song was recorded by Marty Robbins, Bob Dylan, the
Stylistics, Shirley Bassey, and Engelbert Humperdinck.
Through the decades, European artists, including Swedish pop group A-Teens, and British reggae and pop group
UB40, recorded their own versions, and grunge band Pearl Jam has covered it at their concerts.
Newer versions continue to be recorded by newer artists, such as Kacey Musgraves
who recorded a version in 2022 for a movie about Elvis Presley.
This song was ranked one of the greatest songs of
all-time by Rolling Stone Magazine.
In 2012, it was ranked at No.
The film explores themes of birthday party, hospital, medical
school, philanthropy, emergency medical technician (emt).
The tone is emotional.